Register to The Leroy Anderson Papers
Yale University Music Library
- Music, Series I
  - Emperor Waltz, score (8 p.) (Box 6, Folder 189)
  - Empty Hands, condensed score (2 p.) (Box 6, Folder 190)
  - Entr'acte, score (11 p.) (Box 6, Folder 191)
  - Entr'acte, score (8 p.) (Box 6, Folder 192)
  - España Waltz, score (8 p.) (Box 6, Folder 193)
  - Fair Enough (Hasty Pudding Show) Mills Music, Inc., c1939; 4 vocal scores (11 p. total) (Box 25, Folder 838)
    includes program.
  - Farewell, My Lovely, score (8 p.) (Box 6, Folder 194)
  - Fiddle-Faddle Mills Music Inc., c1947; score (18 p.) & parts (Box 6, Folder 195)
  - Fiddle-Faddle, c1970; score (17 p.) & parts (Box 6, Folder 196)
    ed. Samuel Applebaum
  - Fiddle-Faddle Mills Music Inc., c1949 (Box 6, Folder 197)
  - Fiddle-Faddle Mills Music Inc., c1947; score (8 p.) & part (Box 6, Folder 198)
    xylophone, marimba or vibraphone & piano
  - Fiddle-Faddle Mills Music Ltd., c1948; parts (11 p.) (Box 6, Folder 199)
  - Fiddle-Faddle Mills Music Ltd., c1948; score (7 p.) (Box 6, Folder 200)
  - Fiddle-Faddle Mills Music Ltd., c1948; score (8 p.) (Box 6, Folder 201)
  - Fiddle-Faddle Mills Music Inc., c1953; score (7 p.) (Box 6, Folder 202)
    2 copies. Hammond registration.
  - Fiddle-Faddle Mills Music Inc., c1957; score (7 p.) (Box 6, Folder 203)
  - Fiddle-Faddle Mills Music Inc., c1948; score (8 p.) & parts (Box 6, Folder 204)
  - Fiddle-Faddle Mills Music Inc., c1949; score (5 p.) (Box 6, Folder 205)
    Arranged for "simplified piano solo."
  - Fiddle-Faddle Mills Music Inc., c1948; score (8 p.) & part (Box 6, Folder 206)
  - Fiddle-Faddle Mills Music Inc., c1948; score (11 p.) (Box 6, Folder 207)
  - Fiddle-Faddle Editora Musical Mills Ltda., c1959; score (7 p.) (Box 6, Folder 208)
  - Fiddle-Faddle Mills Music, Belgium, c1947; score (5 p.) (Box 6, Folder 209)
  - Fiddle-Faddle Mills Music Inc., c1948; score (7 p.) (Box 6, Folder 210)
  - Fiddle-Faddle Mills Music Inc., c1948; score (7 p.) (Box 6, Folder 211)
    trans. Charles Nunzio
    "First printing" and "corrected file" copies.
  - Fiddle-Faddle Mills Music Inc., c1948; condensed score (10 p.) & parts (Box 6, Folder 212)
  - Fiddle-Faddle Mills Music Inc., c1949; condensed score (8 p.) & parts (Box 6, Folder 213)
    arr. Philip J. Lang
  - Fiddle-Faddle Mills Music Inc., c1953; score (7 p.) & part (Box 6, Folder 214)
  - Fiddle-Faddle, score (10 p.) (Box 23, Folder 796)
    string orchestra and piano (optional)
    Ink with pencil additions.
  - Fiddle-Faddle, vocal score (5 p.) (Box 25, Folder 839)
    words by Mitchell Parish
  - Fiddle-Faddle Mills Music, Inc., c1947; vocal score (5 p.) (Box 25, Folder 840)
  - Fiddle-Faddle (sketch), condensed score (4 p.) (Box 25, Folder 841)
  - Fiddle-Faddle (sketch), score (5 p.) (Box 25, Folder 842)
    harp
  - Finale, score (2 p.) (Box 6, Folder 215)
  - Finale, score (2 p.) (Box 6, Folder 216)
  - Finale (6/8), score (1 p.) (Box 6, Folder 217)
  - First Dartmouth Medley, score (14 p.) (Box 6, Folder 218)
  - First Day of Spring, The, 6/28/54; score (8 p.) (Box 6, Folder 219)
  - First Day of Spring, The Mills Music Inc., c1954; score (5 p.) (Box 6, Folder 221)
  - First Day of Spring, The Mills Music Inc., c1956; score (10 p.) & parts (Box 6, Folder 222)
  - First Day of Spring, The (O Primeiro Dia da Primavera) Editora Musical Mills Ltda., c1959; score (3 p.) (Box 6, Folder 220)
  - Fishing, condensed score (2 p.) (Box 7, Folder 223)
  - Foggy Day, score (2 p.) (Box 7, Folder 224)
  - Forgotten Dreams, 5/28/54; score (7 p.) (Box 7, Folder 225)
    Pencil. "Original score used for first recording."
  - Forgotten Dreams, score (7 p.) (Box 7, Folder 226)
    "Edited score used for print." Penciled corrections and additions.
  - Forgotten Dreams Mills Music Ltd., c1954; condensed score (3 p.) & parts (Box 7, Folder 227)
    arr. Les Williams
    2 copies. English edition.
  - Forgotten Dreams Mills Music Ltd., c1954; condensed score (4 p.) & parts (Box 7, Folder 228)
  - Forgotten Dreams Mills Music Ltd., c1954; score (3 p.) (Box 7, Folder 229)
  - Forgotten Dreams Mills Music Ltd., c1957; score (3 p.) (Box 7, Folder 230)
    arr. Eric Steiner
  - Forgotten Dreams Mills Music Ltd., c1954; score (3 p.) (Box 7, Folder 231)
    arr. Camilleri
  - Forgotten Dreams Mills Music Ltd., c1954; score (5 p.) (Box 7, Folder 232)
  - Forgotten Dreams Mills Music Ltd., c1954; condensed score (3 p.) & parts (Box 7, Folder 233)
    arr. Geoffrey Brand
  - Forgotten Dreams, c1981; score (4 p.) (Box 7, Folder 234)
  - Forgotten Dreams, c1962; score (3 p.) (Box 7, Folder 235)
  - Forgotten Dreams Mills Music Inc., c1962; score (5 p.) (Box 7, Folder 236)
  - Forgotten Dreams Rolfe Budde Musikverlag, c1954; score (2 p.) (Box 7, Folder 237)
  - Forgotten Dreams Mills Music Inc., c1954; score (5 p.) (Box 7, Folder 238)
  - Forgotten Dreams Mills Music Inc., c1955; score (8 p.), condensed score (3 p.) & parts (Box 7, Folder 239)
  - Forgotten Dreams Mills Music Inc., c1956; score (7 p.), condensed score (4 p.) & parts (Box 7, Folder 240)
  - Forgotten Dreams., score (7 p.) (Box 25, Folder 843)
  - Forgotten Dreams (sketch), condensed score (4 p.) (Box 25, Folder 844)
  - Forgotten Dreams (Sogni Dimenticati), c1954; condensed score (3 p.) & parts (Box 7, Folder 241)
    Music for "Till" on reverse side of all parts. Italian lyrics by Ardo. Italian edition.
  - Forgotten Dreams (Sogni Dimenticati), c1954; score (2 p.) (Box 7, Folder 242)
    "Professional copy." Italian lyrics by Ardo. Italian edition.
  - Freshman on Main Street (sketch), condensed score (4 p.) (Box 25, Folder 845)
  - Fun's Fun, score (4 p.) (Box 7, Folder 243)
  - Giovinezza, score (4 p.) (Box 7, Folder 244)
  - Girl Crazy - Selection (sketch), [11] p. of music (Box 23, Folder 797)
    [George Gershwin]
  - Girl I Left Behind Me (sketch), condensed score ([4] p.) (Box 23, Folder 798)
    orchestra, note: organ (optional) Recommend
  - Girl I Left Behind Me, The, score (34 p.) (Box 7, Folder 245)
  - Girl I Left Behind Me, The Mills Music Inc., c1950; condensed score (8 p.) & parts (Box 7, Folder 246)
  - Girl I Left Behind Me, The Mills Music Inc., c1953; condensed score (8 p.) & parts (Box 7, Folder 247)
  - Girl I Left Behind Me, The, 8/19/57; score (35 p.) (Box 25, Folder 846)
    Penciled additions and corrections.
  - Girl I Left Behind Me, The (sketch), condensed score (9 p.) (Box 25, Folder 847)
  - Girl in Satin (Zwei blaue Augen ein weisses Kleid), c1957; score (3 p.) (Box 7, Folder 248)
    Teoton-Verlag
  - Girl In Satin, The Mills Music Inc., c1954 (Box 7, Folder 249)
  - Girl in Satin, The, 8/27/53; score (11 p.) & "piano solo" arrangement (Box 7, Folder 250)
  - Girl in Satin, The Mills Music Ltd., c1954; condensed score (4 p.) & parts (Box 7, Folder 251)
  - Girl in Satin, The Mills Music Ltd., c1953; score (5 p.) (Box 7, Folder 252)
  - Girl in Satin, The Mills Music Ltd., c1954 (Box 7, Folder 253)
  - Girl in Satin, The Mills Music Ltd., c1954; condensed score/solo cornet (2 p.) & parts (Box 7, Folder 254)
  - Girl in Satin, The Mills Music Inc., c1953; score (5 p.) (Box 7, Folder 255)
  - Girl In Satin, The Mills Music Inc., c1953; condensed score (4 p.) & parts (Box 7, Folder 256)
  - Girl In Satin, The Mills Music Inc., c1953; condensed score (4 p.) & parts (Box 7, Folder 257)
  - Girl in Satin, The, 10/18/55; score (12 p.) (Box 25, Folder 848)
  - Girl in Satin, The (Das Mädchen in Seide), c1955; score (3 p.) (Box 7, Folder 258)
    German edition. 2 copies.
  - Girl In Satin, The (sketch), condensed score (5 p.) (Box 25, Folder 849)
  - Girl in Satin, The (sketch), condensed score (1 p.) (Box 25, Folder 850)
  - Give 'Em the Eye, condensed score (2 p.) (Box 7, Folder 259)
  - Give Me a Chance, score (3 p.) (Box 7, Folder 260)
  - Give Me One Hour, 12/12/48; condensed score (3 p.) (Box 7, Folder 261)
  - Glad to be Unhappy, condensed score (1 p.) (Box 7, Folder 262)
  - Gloria Musik Box no. 35 Gloria Musikverlag, score (15 p.) (Box 8, Folder 263)
    Anthology of compositions by various composers including Anderson's "The Girl In Satin." German edition.
  - Gold and Silver, 10/18/39; score (8 p.) (Box 8, Folder 264)
  - Golden Years, The Woodbury Music Corporation, c1963; score (19 p.) & parts (Box 8, Folder 265)
  - Golden Years, The Woodbury Music Corporation, 1/30/63 - c1962; score (16 p.) (Box 8, Folder 266)
  - Golden Years, The Woodbury Music Corporation, 5/31/62; score (17 p.) (Box 8, Folder 267)
  - Golden Years, The Woodbury Music Corporation, c1962; score (5 p.) (Box 8, Folder 268)
  - Golden Years, The Woodbury Music Corporation, c1963; score (19 p.), condensed score (8 p.) & parts (Box 8, Folder 269)
  - Golden Years, The (sketch), condensed score (5 p.) (Box 25, Folder 851)
  - Goldilocks, score (ca. 200 p.) (Box 27, Folder 270)
    Withdrawn.
  - Goldilocks, holograph score (2 copies) & parts (each part a book of loose sheets ca. 125-150 p.) (Box 28–32)
    manuscript/photocopy
    orchestra (parts for: vlA-D/vla/cello/bass/harp(2)/reed1-5 /tpt1-3/tbn1-2/piano/conductor/piano-conductor masters/choral parts)
    Also included are 4 copies of the text and lyric book.
    One includes penciled corrections.
  - Goldilocks - Dance Music, loose sheets (ca. 100 p.) (Box 8, Folder 272)
    manuscript
  - Goldilocks Overture (Box 8, Folder 273)
  - Goldilocks Vocal Selection Ankerford Music Corporation, c1959; score (31 p.) (Box 8, Folder 274)
  - Goodbye, Now, condensed score (1 p.) (Box 8, Folder 275)
  - Got a Bran' New Suit (at Home Abroad), score (4 p.) (Box 8, Folder 276)
  - Governor Bradford March, 5/24/48; score (20 p.) (Box 23, Folder 799)
  - Governor Bradford March (sketch), 5/24/40; condensed score (5 p.) (Box 25, Folder 852)
  - Greatest Hits of Leroy Anderson vol. 1 & 2 Toa Music Company, c1978; scores (vol. 1 - 32 p./vol. 2 - 31 p.) (Box 8, Folder 277)
    vocal trio, electric organ & percussion
  - Green-eyed Dragon, The, 12/26/48; condensed score (4 p.) (Box 8, Folder 278)
  - Hallelujah, condensed score (3 p.) (Box 8, Folder 279)
  - Happy Times, 12/17/33 (Box 8, Folder 280)
    vocal score
    Pencil. Arrangement of "Today I Feel So Happy" on reverse side.
  - Harvard Fantasy, score (41 p.) (Box 23, Folder 800)
    Note on title page: First performance - June 16, 1936 Written for reunion of class of 1911
  - Harvard Medley, score (19 p.) (Box 8, Folder 281)
  - Harvard Sketches, score (20 p.) (Box 8, Folder 282)
    Pencil. "First performance: May 15, 1939 Boston Pops, Leroy Anderson guest conductor. Rewritten as 'Alma Mater', 1954."
  - Harvard Sketches, score (7, 8, 7, 16 p.) (Box 23, Folder 801)
    Note on cover: 1st perf Harvard ? 1938
  - Have You Met Miss Jones?, score (5 p.) (Box 8, Folder 283)
  - Heart of a Fool, score (5 p.) (Box 8, Folder 284)
  - Heart of Stone (Pyramid Dance) Ankerford Music Corporation, c1958; score (5 p.) (Box 8, Folder 285)
    From the musical "Goldilocks."
  - Heart of Stone (Pyramid Dance) Mills Music Inc., c1960; score (21 p.) (Box 8, Folder 286)
  - Holy City, The, 12/19/48; condensed score (4 p.) (Box 8, Folder 287)
  - Holy Cross Medley, score (16 p.) (Box 8, Folder 288)
  - Holy Cross Song, score (4 p.) (Box 8, Folder 289)
  - Home Stretch Galop Woodbury Music Corporation, c1963; score (28 p.) & parts (Box 9, Folder 290)
  - Home Stretch Galop, 1/13/63; score (27 p.) (Box 9, Folder 291)
  - Home Stretch Galop, 5/22/62; score (27 p.) (Box 9, Folder 292)
  - Home Stretch Galop Woodbury Music Corporation, c1962; score (7 p.) (Box 9, Folder 293)
  - Home Stretch Galop Woodbury Music Corporation, c1964; score (28 p.), condensed score (16 p.) & parts (Box 9, Folder 294)
  - Home Stretch: Galop (sketch), condensed score (7 p.) (Box 25, Folder 853)
  - Hoopercliffe, score (2 p.) (Box 9, Folder 295)
  - Horse and Buggy, c1983; score (12 p.) & parts (Box 9, Folder 296)
  - Horse and Buggy Mills Music Ltd., c1953; condensed score (8 p.) (Box 9, Folder 297)
  - Horse and Buggy Mills Music Ltd., c1951; score (6 p.) (Box 9, Folder 298)
  - Horse and Buggy Mills Music Ltd., c1953; condensed score (3 p.) & parts (Box 9, Folder 299)
    arr. Bernard Ebbinghouse
  - Horse and Buggy Mills Music Inc., c1951; score (7 p.) (Box 9, Folder 300)
  - Horse and Buggy Mills Music Inc., c1952; score (5 p.) (Box 9, Folder 301)
  - Horse and Buggy Mills Music Inc., c1952; condensed score (8 p.) & parts (Box 9, Folder 302)
  - Horse and Buggy Mills Music Inc., c1952; condensed score (12 p.) & parts (Box 9, Folder 303)
  - Horse and Buggy, 1/13/52 (Box 24, Folder 802)
    score (26 leaves)
    Ink with red and blue pencil additions.
  - Horse and Buggy (sketch), 6/11/51; condensed score (7 p.) (Box 25, Folder 854)
  - Hurry Music, score (2 p.) (Box 9, Folder 304)
  - Hurry Music, score (4 p.) (Box 9, Folder 305)
  - Hussars March, score (6 p.) (Box 9, Folder 306)
  - I Concentrate on You, score (9 p.) (Box 9, Folder 307)
  - I Fall In Love With You, score (6 p.) (Box 9, Folder 308)
  - I Give In, condensed score (1 p.) (Box 9, Folder 309)
  - I Got Plenty O' Nuttin', 1/16/49; condensed score (3 p.) (Box 9, Folder 310)
  - I Love Thee, 3/6/49; condensed score (2 p.) (Box 9, Folder 311)
  - I Need Inspiration, condensed score (1 p.) (Box 9, Folder 312)
  - I Never Know When, score (11 p.) (Box 9, Folder 313)
  - I Never Know When to Say When Ankerford Music Corporation, c1958; score (5 p.) (Box 9, Folder 314)
  - I Never Know When to Say When (sketch), condensed score (3 p.) (Box 25, Folder 855)
  - I Whistle a Happy Tune, condensed score (5 p.) (Box 9, Folder 315)
  - I Whistle a Happy Tune, score (17 p.) (Box 25, Folder 856)
  - I'll Always Be With You, score (1 p.), vocal part (1 p.) (Box 9, Folder 316)
  - I'll Take Romance, score (4 p.) (Box 9, Folder 317)
    Pencil. "For Willie Morris."
  - I'll Take You Home Again, Kathleen, 3/13/49; condensed score (3 p.) (Box 9, Folder 318)
  - I'm Always In the Mood for You, score (5 p.) (Box 9, Folder 319)
  - I'm Falling In Love With Some One, 2/13/49; condensed score (4 p.) (Box 9, Folder 320)
  - I'm Putting All My Eggs In One Basket, 2/10/36; score (4 p.) (Box 9, Folder 321)
  - I'm the Echo (I Dream too Much), 12/11/35; score (4 p.) (Box 9, Folder 322)
  - I've a Good Imagination, score (1 p.) & lyrics sheet (Box 9, Folder 323)
    Francis Johnson
  - If and When, 12/30/40; score (3 p.) (Box 10, Folder 324)
    Pencil. "For Ruby Newman - Brown Show 1941."
  - If You Dare, condensed score (3 p.) (Box 10, Folder 325)
  - Imagination, condensed score (7 p.) (Box 10, Folder 326)
  - Imagination, score (2 p.) (Box 10, Folder 327)
  - In the Gloaming, 1/9/49; condensed score (4 p.) (Box 10, Folder 328)
  - In the Still of the Night, 3/27/49; condensed score (4 p.) (Box 10, Folder 329)
  - Invitation to the Dance Waltz, 1/1/39; score (5 p.) (Box 10, Folder 330)
  - Irish Suite, score (154 p.) (Box 10, Folder 331)
    photocopy
  - Irish Suite Part II ("The Wearing of the Green"), condensed score (11 p.) (Box 10, Folder 332)
    Pencil. "For Arthur Fiedler."
  - Irish Washerwoman, The Mills Music Inc., c1953; condensed score (8 p.) & parts (Box 10, Folder 333)
  - Irish Washerwoman, The (from the Irish Suite), 7/21/50; score (34 p.) (Box 25, Folder 857)
    Penciled additions and corrections
  - Irish Washerwoman, The (Irish Suite) (sketch), condensed score (9 p.) (Box 25, Folder 858)
  - Isn't This a Lovely Day, score (4 p.) (Box 10, Folder 334)
  - It Might as Well be Spring, 5/4/46; score (16 p.) (Box 10, Folder 335)
  - It Might As Well Be Spring, score (16 p.) (Box 24, Folder 803)
    Ink with pencil and red pencil additions. From State Fair.
  - It Seems to be Spring, score (1 p.) (Box 10, Folder 336)
  - It's Got To Be Love, score (4 p.) (Box 10, Folder 337)
  - It's Like Reaching for the Moon, 4/17/36; score (7 p.) (Box 10, Folder 338)
  - It's the Natural Thing to Do, score (6 p.) (Box 10, Folder 339)
  - Jazz Legato Mills Music Inc., c1944; score (7 p.) & parts (Box 10, Folder 340)
  - Jazz Legato Mills Music Inc., c1945 (Box 10, Folder 341)
    arr. Will Hudson
  - Jazz Legato, score (11 p.) (Box 10, Folder 342)
  - Jazz Legato Mills Music Ltd., c1945; parts (7 p.) (Box 10, Folder 343)
  - Jazz Legato Mills Music Ltd., c1944; score (4 p.) (Box 10, Folder 344)
  - Jazz Legato Mills Music Ltd., c1944; score (4 p.) (Box 10, Folder 345)
  - Jazz Legato Mills Music Ltd., c1945; parts (7 p.) (Box 10, Folder 346)
  - Jazz Legato Mills Music Inc., c1953; score (6 p.) (Box 10, Folder 347)
  - Jazz Legato Mills Music Inc., c1948; score (5 p.) & parts (Box 10, Folder 348)
  - Jazz Legato Mills Music Inc., c1948; score (5 p.) & part (Box 10, Folder 349)
  - Jazz Legato Mills Music Inc., c1945; parts (7 p.) (Box 10, Folder 350)
    arr. J. Louis Merkur
  - Jazz Legato Mills Music Inc., c1944; score (5 p.) (Box 10, Folder 351)
  - Jazz Legato Mills Music Inc., c1949; score (5 p.) (Box 10, Folder 352)
  - Jazz Legato Mills Music Inc., c1949; condensed score (3 p.) & parts (Box 10, Folder 353)
  - Jazz Legato, score ([4] p.) (Box 24, Folder 804)
    Ink with pencil and red and blue pencil additions. Note: original score
  - Jazz Legato (sketch), vocal score (5 p.) (Box 25, Folder 859)
  - Jazz Legato (sketch), score (4 p.) (Box 25, Folder 860)
  - Jazz Pizzicato Mills Music Inc., c1967; score (5 p.) & parts (Box 10, Folder 354)
  - Jazz Pizzicato Mills Music Inc., c1939; score (4 p.) & parts (Box 10, Folder 355)
  - Jazz Pizzicato, c1981; score (7 p.) & parts (Box 10, Folder 356)
  - Jazz Pizzicato Mills Music Inc., c1945 (Box 10, Folder 357)
  - Jazz Pizzicato Mills Music Inc., c1946 (Box 10, Folder 358)
    arr. Jimmy Dale
  - Jazz Pizzicato Mills Music Inc., c1949; score (4 p.) & parts (Box 10, Folder 359)
  - Jazz Pizzicato Mills Music Ltd., c1945; parts (7 p.) (Box 10, Folder 360)
  - Jazz Pizzicato Mills Music Ltd., c1939; score (4 p.) (Box 11, Folder 361)
  - Jazz Pizzicato Mills Music Inc., c1953; score (5 p.) (Box 11, Folder 362)
  - Jazz Pizzicato Mills Music Inc., c1948; score (5 p.) & parts (Box 11, Folder 363)
  - Jazz Pizzicato Mills Music Inc., c1948; score (5 p.) & part (Box 11, Folder 364)
  - Jazz Pizzicato, c1984; score (4 p.) (Box 11, Folder 365)
  - Jazz Pizzicato Mills Music Inc., c1945; parts (7 p.) (Box 11, Folder 366)
  - Jazz Pizzicato Mills Music Inc., c1944; score (5 p.) (Box 11, Folder 367)
  - Jazz Pizzicato Mills Music Inc., c1949; score (5 p.) (Box 11, Folder 368)
  - Jazz Pizzicato Mills Music Inc., c1964; score (12 p.) (Box 11, Folder 369)
    arr. Ralph Hunter
    mixed voices & rhythm-combo
  - Jazz Pizzicato Mills Music Inc., c1948; condensed score (4 p.) & parts (Box 11, Folder 370)
  - Jazz Pizzicato, score (5 p.) (Box 24, Folder 805)
    Ink with pencil and blue pencil additions. On first page: Mills Music Inc....
  - Jazz Pizzicato (sketch) Mills Music, Inc., c1939, 1950; vocal score (5 p.) (Box 25, Folder 861)
    with typescript and manuscript lyrics (3 p.)
  - Jazz Pizzicato (sketch), vocal score (5 p.) (Box 25, Folder 862)
  - Jericho (Swing Fugue), condensed score (6 p.) (Box 11, Folder 371)
  - Just a Salesgirl, condensed score (2 p.) (Box 11, Folder 372)
  - Kappa Kappa, score (3 p.) (Box 11, Folder 373)
  - Kiss Me, Kate Selection, 5/9/49; condensed score (16 p.) (Box 11, Folder 374)
  - Lady in Waiting Ankerford Music Corporation, c1958; score (5 p.) (Box 11, Folder 375)
  - Lady in Waiting Ankerford Music Corporation, c1961; score (5 p.) (Box 11, Folder 376)
    From the musical "Goldilocks." 2 copies.
  - Lady in Waiting - Ballet Music, score (49 p.) (Box 11, Folder 377)
  - Lady in Waiting - Ballet Music (sketch), condensed score (13 p.) (Box 25, Folder 863)
  - Lady in Waiting - Waltz (sketch), condensed score (7 p.) (Box 25, Folder 864)
  - Last Rose of Summer, The (sketch), condensed score (3 p.) (Box 25, Folder 865)
  - Lazy Moon Ankerford Music Corp., c1958 (Box 11, Folder 378)
  - Lazy Moon Ankerford Music Corporation, c1958; score (5 p.) (Box 11, Folder 379)
    From the Musical "Goldilocks."
  - Leroy Anderson (Almost Complete), c1978; score (121 p.) (Box 11, Folder 380)
    "25 great melodies as originally composed for piano solo."
  - Leroy Anderson Favorites for Conn Organs Mills Music Inc., c1957; score (36 p.) (Box 11, Folder 382)
    Anthology of 8 compositions. 3 copies.
  - Leroy Anderson Favorites for Gulbransen Organs Mills Music Inc., c1961; score (36 p.) (Box 11, Folder 383)
    registrations by Norm Nelson
    Anthology of 8 compositions. 2 copies.
  - Leroy Anderson Favorites for Hammond Organs Mills Music Inc., c1958; score (36 p.) (Box 11, Folder 381)
    arr. Sam Keck
    Anthology of 8 compositions.
  - Leroy Anderson Portrait, score (24 p.) & parts (Box 11, Folder 384)
    arr. James Barnes
  - Leroy Anderson Suite, A, c1984; score (14 p.) (Box 11, Folder 385)
    arr. Gregg Nestor
    guitar
  - Leroy Anderson's Best Belwin Mills/Mills Music Inc., c1970; score (30 p.) (Box 11, Folder 386)
    arr. Mark Nevin
    Anthology of 10 compositions. "Easy piano arrangements."
  - Leroy Anderson's Music Rolf Budde Musikverlag, score (37 p.) (Box 11, Folder 387)
    Collection of 8 compositions. German edition.
  - Let 'Em Eat Cake, score (4 p.) (Box 11, Folder 388)
  - Let Me Live It Again, score (1 p.) (Box 11, Folder 389)
  - Library Reading Room (sketch), condensed score (3 p.) (Box 25, Folder 866)
  - Life of a Faculty Wife, score (7 p.) (Box 11, Folder 390)
  - Little Girls Should Be Seen, 14/9/58; score (63 p.) (Box 25, Folder 867)
    copyist's manuscript
  - Little Picture Playhouse, condensed score (6 p.) (Box 11, Folder 391)
  - Lock Your Heart, score (3 p.) (Box 11, Folder 392)
  - Lord Geoffrey Amherst, score (4 p.) (Box 11, Folder 393)
  - Lotus Flower, condensed score (2 p.) (Box 11, Folder 394)
    Dorothy Lucas Higginson
  - Love Is a Dancing Thing, condensed score (4 p.) (Box 11, Folder 395)
  - Lover, score (10 p.) (Box 11, Folder 397)
  - Love's Old, Sweet Song, 1/16/49; condensed score (2 p.) (Box 11, Folder 396)
  - Loving You, score (1 p.) (Box 11, Folder 398)
  - March, score (12 p.) (Box 11, Folder 399)
    Winslow Sears
  - March in D/Czecho-Slovakian Dance Song, score (2 p.) & parts (Box 11, Folder 400)
    Vladimir Rebikoff
    Pencil. For 1935 Vincent Club show. Also includes sheet music of "March in D" and "Czecho-Slovakian Dance Song" used for arrangements.
  - Medley, score (9 p.) (Box 11, Folder 401)
    Pencil. "For Felix Meyer."
  - Mildew, We Love You, condensed score (2 p.) (Box 11, Folder 402)
  - Mills' Evergreen Album Band 1 Mills Musikverlag, score (30 p.) (Box 11, Folder 404)
    Collection of 12 compositions including 2 by Anderson.
  - Mills' Evergreen Album Band 2 Mills Musikverlag, score (30 p.) (Box 11, Folder 403)
    Collection of 12 compositions including 5 by Anderson.
  - Minstrel Boy, The Mills Music Inc., c1960; score (16 p.), condensed score (8 p.) & parts (Box 12, Folder 405)
  - Minstrel Boy, The (from the Irish Suite), score (16 p.) (Box 25, Folder 868)
  - Minstrel Boy, The (sketch), condensed score (4 p.) (Box 25, Folder 869)
  - [Miscellaneous Sketches], (9 p.) (Box 26, Folder 908)
  - Moon Got In My Eyes, The, score (4 p.) (Box 12, Folder 406)
  - Moonrise on the Lowlands, score (5 p.) (Box 12, Folder 407)
  - Music from Vincent Ventures, c1934; vocal score (19 p.) (Box 25, Folder 870)
    includes program from Vincent Ventures 1935
  - Music of Leroy Anderson, The Mills Music Inc., c1962 (Box 12, Folder 410)
    score & part
  - Music of Leroy Anderson, The Mills Music Ltd., c1951; score (64 p.) (Box 12, Folder 413)
    Anthology of Leroy Anderson music: includes 14 compositions.
  - Music of Leroy Anderson, The Belwin Mills/Mills Music, c1965; score (48 p.) (Box 12, Folder 414)
  - Music of Leroy Anderson, The (Vol. 1) Mills Music Inc., c1961 (Box 12, Folder 408)